Hello friends welcome to TV Tower.
Due to an accident at home these days I am
unable to make any videos but in the
meantime I need something related to a
tooth and this is just
taking something about it today how can you see
that this is just
Rupesh remaking it that I
made such a video for the first time but during that time there was
some problem in this my
personal information was leaked so it was
arrested by YouTube and there was talk of removing it
so I am telling all these things about this chilli parking
it will be visible its
information is shifted in two pots basic
paudi then in rumor this premium you must be
seeing this 1000 steps 10940
porn which is silver that extra
its cost is 311 311 and roadside
assistant 119 1604
1604 so from basic 68 liability its
forfeit
500 and UPA and driver
ghee 270 rupees and both together it is 0
500 which is
without
taste  And
that is what has happened, by
combining both of them, the
force in this is six and the final
premium amount of texture Arjun will be seen like this, that is
Z1 Shyam
Shyam and the list of the car, the total
payment that I had made was around 150 300 and
this Dixit's car, this is our
institute, secondly, see, you have
total IDBI John Rafi
50, so what I had set in this is
130000, in this,
this film subsidy is only after reducing it
and apart from that, at the moment I got its subsidy,
I don't know about the state subsidy, I got a
call in the fight for the screen, in which it was
said that you will get an OTP, you will have to share the OTP
and it will go to your station,
but I refused for that, I do
n't know, many frauds are happening,
instead of profit, there may be loss,
so friends, you will be able to get the film video
in bulk after the 11th, when
I am not able to go out of the house in my hair,
if you start seeing information, then
share it and also
definitely subscribe to the channel, the
subscription rate is quite useful,
according to the number of people watching, about one
percent  If you are not subscribing, you will see it
and I will discuss new baby possibilities related to Uttarakhand or hilly
areas
and
what possibilities can be created, you will
see these in the future videos that will be made.